The Lucky Ones is a comedy, drama, history film directed by Neil Burger.
The story revolves around three soldiers — Colee, T.K.
and Cheaver — who return from the Iraq War after suffering
injuries and learn that life has moved on without them.
They end up on an unexpected road trip across the U.S.
Colee Dunn, played by Rachel McAdams.
Fred Cheaver, played by Tim Robbins.
T.K. Poole, played by Michael Peña.
Jeanie Klinger, played by Annie Corley.
Tom Klinger, played by John Diehl.
Bob, played by John Heard.
The Lucky Ones is a 2007 American comedy-drama directed by Neil Burger
and stars Tim Robbins, Rachel McAdams and Michael Peña.
The screenplay by Burger and Dirk Wittenborn focuses on three United States Army
soldiers who find themselves drawn together by unforeseen circumstances.
The film was released in the US on September 26th,
2008 and was a box office bomb.
The film explores themes of friendship, road trip, soldier.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.